Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Irish Americana Collection AIA.031.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Ephemera, 1833-1961
  - Sub-series VI.A: General, 1833-1961
    - Trade Cards, undated (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Weller & Graham, map of Ireland, undated (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Sub-series VI.B: Merchant Ads, 1916-circa 1960
    - Vacuum Harness Oil, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Arbuckle Bros. Coffee Co., undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Crescent Wash Board, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Arbuckle's Ariosa Coffee, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Arbuckle's Ariosa Coffee, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Arbuckle's Ariosa Coffee, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Arbuckle's Ariosa Coffee, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Arbuckle's Ariosa Coffee, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Arbuckle's Ariosa Coffee, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Wilson Yeast and MANFG Company, Limited, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Neal's Carriage Paints, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - "Ariosa Coffee", undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - "Ariosa Coffee", undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Saginaw Manufacturing Co., undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - A New Vehicle, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Pond's Extract, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Schultz's Irish Soap, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - McSorley's Inflation, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Mr. Edison's Wonderful New Phonograph, Nov, 1916 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - "Have a Coke = Cead Míle Fáilte," Coca-Cola (ad), 1943 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Victor Records (ad), Ladies Home Journal, Feb, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Valiant (ad), circa 1960s (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Irish International Airlines (ad), 1963 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - The Luck of the Irish (ad), 1948 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Shillelagh Apples (ad), undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Welcome Answer, The, undated (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Jameson's Irish American Whiskey (ad), undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Columbia Hour of Musical Broadcasting, Oct 1, 1927 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Victor - Victrola, Mar 29, 1913 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Irish Airlines (ad), circa 1960s (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Globe Clothing House (ad), undated (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Irish Eyes Are Smiling Movie Advertisement, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 162, Folder 5)
    - Irish Advertisements, 1900, 1916, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 164, Folder 2)
  - Sub-series VI.C: Cartoons, 1865-1892
    - Life in New York, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - The Fenian Pest, Punch, March 3, 1866 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Disendowment and Disarmament, Punch, April 13, 1869 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - An Irish Wake, Harper's Weekly, March 15, 1873 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - An Axe to Grind, Weekly National Press, Jan, 1892 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Speak or Die!, Weekly National Press, Mar, 1892 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - The Irish Skirmishers 'Blind Pool', Puck, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Last Reception of the Season, Puck, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - O'Donovan Rossa's Shooting Gallery, Puck, undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral, Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, June 7, 1879 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Fenian Congress, Harper's Weekly, Nov. 4, 1865 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Land Agitation, Harper's Weekly, 1880 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Europe, Church & State, United States, Harper's Weekly, Feb. 1870 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Would You Marry Your Daughter to a Nigger?, Harper's Weekly, July 1, 1868 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - The Irish Tempest, Punch, March 19, 1870 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - The Irish Treason Shop, Punch, Dec. 4, 1869 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Leading Him a Lively Dance (cartoon), undated (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Round the Cauldron, Punch, March 26, 1887 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Waiting for the Return of a Sunday Excursion, The Judge, July 15, 1882 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - St. Patrick in New York, Harper's Weekly, April 2, 1870 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Roman Cathlics Disgracing Themselves, Harper's Weekly, May 7, 1870 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Champion of the Fenians, Harper's Weekly, Oct. 21, 1876 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - The Usual Irish Way of Doing Things, Harper's Weekly, Sept. 2, 1871 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Little Orphan Annie, New York Herald, 1904 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - An Xmas Greeting to Waterford, Weekly National Press, 1891 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Political Cartoons, 1884, 1888-1891 (Box Shared Tamiment 161, Folder 5, Box Shared Tamiment 164, Folder 4)
    - Various, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - The Punch Bowl, Killarney, undated (Box 58, Folder 20)